选张牌  任何一张
Okay, pick a card, any card.
好  记住它
All right, now memorize it.
让大家看
Show it to everybody.
好了吗
Got it? Mm-hm.
好  还给我
All right. Give it back to me.
红心五
Five of hearts.
魔术真是神奇
Real magic does exist.Oh, wow.
乔伊  你怎么变的
Wow. Joey, how do you do it?
无可奉告
I can't tell you that. No.
有人在天花板上敲门
Uh, somebody's at the door on the ceiling.
不  那是我们楼上邻居的噪音
Heh. No, that's our unbelievably loud upstairs neighbor.
他收起地毯  所有声音一清二楚
He took up the carpets,and now you can hear everything.
为何不上楼请他放轻脚步
Well, why don't you go up there and ask him to just step lightly, please?
我试过…五次了吧  但那家伙魅力无法挡…
I have, like five times,but the guy is so charming...
我上去骂人  结果反而跟他道歉
...that I go up there to yell,and I end up apologizing to him.
太离谱了
Oh, that is silly.
我上去叫他小声点
I'll go up there.I'll tell him to keep it down.
好啊  请便  祝你好运
All right, be my guest.Good luck.
好吧  好吧…
All right, all right, all right.
如果你们真想知道我怎么变的  我就告诉你们
If you really wanna know how I did it,I'll show you.
你们把牌还给我的时候  趁你们不注意…
When you handed me back the card,what you didn't see was...
我很快的偷看一下  肉眼是看不到的
...I looked at it so fast,it was invisible to the naked eye.
偷看到了
I just did it.
又看了一次
Just did it again.
来  我放慢速度给你们看  准备好了吗
Here, I'll slow it down so you guys can see it. Ready?
原来如此
Oh. I got it now. Okay.
听着  我朋友住在楼下  你的动静我们听得一清二楚
I was at my friend's downstairs......and we hear every single thing that you do.
谢谢
Oh. Ha, ha. Thank you.
《老友记》 第三季 第11集  见异思迁
Friends S03E11  The One Where Chandler Can't Remember Which Sister
（主演：詹妮弗·安妮斯顿）
（主演：柯特妮·考克斯）
（主演：丽莎·库卓）
（主演：马特·勒布朗）
（主演：马修·派瑞）
（主演：大卫·修蒙）
嘿
Hey.
谁有一条六尺长的绳子  末端还打了个结
Anybody got a length of rope about 6 feet long with a noose at the end?
亲爱的  发生什么事  我刚遇到珍妮丝
Honey, what's the matter? I just saw Janice.
她在洛克斐勒中心  与她先生溜冰
She was at Rockefeller Center,skating with her husband.
看起来很幸福
She looked so happy.
我难过得想拿那孩子的椒盐卷饼扔他们
I almost feel bad for whipping that kid's pretzel at them.
我记得与凯瑟琳分手后第一次偶遇
I remember the first time I saw that girl Katherine after we broke up.
她和好友唐娜在路上有说有笑
She was walking with her friend Donna,just laughing and talking.
天啊  真难过
God, it killed me.
但你那天下午和她们两个上床
Yes, but you ended up having sex with both of them that afternoon.
抱歉  我只是想趁机炫耀这件事
Sorry, I just...Any excuse to tell that story.
钱德  明天会有个派对  你会好过点的
Hey, Chandler, there's a party tomorrow. You'll feel better then.
你知道吗  我没事  不用特地为我举行派对
Oh. You know what? I'm gonna be okay.You don't have to throw a party for me.
是乔伊的生日派对
It's Joey's birthday.
喔  如果要帮某人办派对  那一定是他了
Oh, well, then if anybody should have a party, it should be him.
不敢相信她还在楼上
Shh. I cannot believe she's still up there.
好吧  他完全弄错关键句了
Okay, well,he totally screwed up the punch line.
你知道  应该是…
You know, it's supposed to be:
咖啡好了吗  亲爱的  马上来  卡普兰先生
How's that coffee coming, dear? Yeah. Right away, Mr. Kaplan.
我不该喝咖啡  老是放屁
I'm not supposed to drink coffee.It makes me gassy.
我知道
I know.
你心里一定很纳闷 "这么一个聪慧的女孩…
I'll bet you're thinking,"What's an intelligent girl...
该在时尚业发光发热  怎么会在这泡咖啡"
...who wants to be in fashion doing making coffee?"
你猜对了
Ah? Ah? Ha, ha. Oh, ha, ha. You got me. Heh.
别以为我从没注意到你的潜力
Don't think I haven't noticed your potential.
我有一份与时尚  更有关联的任务给你
Well, I've got a project for you that's a lot more related to fashion.
听起来如何   太棒了
How does that sound? Oh. That sounds great.
过来  亲爱的  太感谢你了  卡普兰先生
Come on over here, sweetheart. Thank you so much, Mr. Kaplan.
我要马上把这些衣架分开
I need these hangers separated ASAP.
不用客气
You're welcome.
老天  我痛恨我的工作
Oh, God, I hate my job.I hate it. I hate my job.
我知道  亲爱的  我很遗憾
I know, honey. I'm sorry.
我想辞职  又觉得该坚持下去
Oh. I wanna quit,but then I think I should stick it out.
我又觉得…
Then I think...
为什么要做这种  有损尊严的工作
...why would such a person stay in such a demeaning job...
难道只因为这份工作  和我的兴趣有一点点关系吗
...just because it's remotely related to the field they're interested in?
我不知道  瑞秋
Gee, I don't know, Rach.
点菜吧  我有杨朵汤  詹姆斯豆  还有木偶餐  随便你点什么都行
Order up. I got a Yentl soup, James Beans,and a Howdy, hold the Doody.
别这样  对不起  我不是…
Oh. Honey, come on, I'm sorry. I didn't...
我不介意吃苦
I don't mind paying my dues.
光是扶着  得了关节炎的
It's just, how much am I gonna learn about fashion...
裁缝师上厕所
...by walking Myra,the arthritic seamstress...
是学不了时尚的
...to the bathroom?
嗨  你是幸灾乐祸吗
Hi. Is my misery amusing to you?
抱歉  我只是…
I'm sorry, I was just, uh... Ha, ha.
不好笑  这就是我的工作
It's not funny. This is actually my job.
相信我  我是过来人
Oh, believe me, I've been there.
我以前专门整理假人模特儿的头
I had to sort mannequin heads at Mannequins Plus.
那么  我要继续跟我朋友聊天
Oh. Well, then, so I'm just gonna go back to talking to my friend here.
你继续享用你的汉堡吧
You can go backto enjoying your little hamburger.
还有一件事   什么
Uh, just one other thing. Ahem. Yes?
我在布鲁明岱尔百货公司上班
I work at Bloomingdale's...
我可能有个你会感兴趣的工作机会
...and I might know of a job possibility,if you're interested.
想吃我的腌黄瓜吗
Do you want my pickle?
大家好
Hey, guys.
嗨  阿甘  嗨
Hey, Gunther.Hi.
你要跟楼上的吵闹家伙约会
You're going out on a date with the noisy guy upstairs?
他很迷人  我知道  他太迷人了
Well, he's very charming. I know, he's too charming.
如果你和他约会  我就更难讨厌他
But if you go out, it's gonna make it so much harder for me to hate him.
你只得尽力而为了
Well, you're just going to have to try.
好了  乔伊  果冻酒呢
All right. Joey?Where are the Jell-O shots?
我不知道  钱德应该端出去
I don't know. Chandler's supposed to be passing them...
钱德  哈罗
Chandler.Hello-dee-lo.
有人心情好多了
Well, somebody's feeling better.
舌头伸出来  上衣脱下来
Stick out your tongue.Take off your shirt.
我的天  老天  喔喔
Oh, my.Oh, my God.
你到底吃了多少  这些是纯伏特加做的
How many of these did you have?These are pure vodka.
是啊  有妈妈的味道
Yeah, Jell-O just like Mom used to make.
我今天遇到一件不可思议的事情
The most unbelievable thing happened to me today.
嗨  嗨
Hi. Hi.
我在摩妮卡的店吃午餐  然后有人与我攀谈·…
I'm having lunch at Monica'sand this guy starts talking to me...
他在布鲁明岱尔百货帮忙采购
...and he works for a buyer at Bloomingdale's...
他的部门有空缺  于是我把电话给了他
...and there's an opening in his department.So I gave him my phone number...
他周末会打给我  看是否能安排面试
...and he's gonna call me this weekend to see if he can get me an interview.
我知道
Wow. Ha, ha. I know.
这个人无缘无故帮你
What, so this guy's helping you for no apparent reason?
完全的陌生人
And he's a total stranger?
对  他叫马克什么的
Yeah. His name is, um, Mark something.
听起来  马克另有所图
Ah. Sounds like "Mark Something" wants to have some sex.
什么
What?
我的意思是  为什么无缘无故给你好处
I'm just saying, why else would he just swoop in out of nowhere for no reason?
想当好人
To be nice?
乔伊  男人会没有理由的  对女性示好吗
Hey, Joey, are men ever nice to strange women for no reason?
不会  除非为了上床  多谢
No, only for sex. Thank you.
你有和马克提到我吗
So did you tell Mark Something about me?
不需要  因为我穿着"我爱罗斯"的广告板
I didn't have to, because I was wearing my "I Heart Ross" sandwich board...
而且摇着铃
...and ringing my bell.
乔伊  生日快乐
Joey! Happy birthday!
嘿
Hey!
好吧  你跟多少女生交往
Okay, how many of that girl are you seeing?
你想哪儿去  那些是乔伊的姊妹
How hammered are you? Huh? These are Joey's sisters.
嗨  乔伊的姊妹
Hi, Joey's sisters.
嗨  你好
Hey.  Hey. Hey.
你在喝什么
What are we drinking over here?
伏特加加小红莓汁
Oh, well, I have a vodka and cranberry juice.
真的
No kidding?
我干掉我先生后  喝的就是这个
That's the exact same drink I made myself right after I shot my husband.
好吧  我不知道该怎么跟你说话
Okay, I don't know how to talk to you.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
把我前任女友的快速拨号键删除
I'm taking my ex-girlfriend off my speed dialer.
不  这是好事
No, no, no, it's a good thing.
我们要快速拨号干嘛  干嘛赶来赶去的
Why must we dial so speedily anyway? Why must we rush through life?
为何不珍惜美好的时光  你的胸部真大
Why can't we savor the precious moments? Those are some huge breasts you have.
嗨  嗨
Hi. Hi.
我听说了瑞秋今天遇见那个叫马克的家伙了
Yeah, heh. So, um, I heard about this Mark guy that Rachel met today.
对  不是很棒吗   是啊
Oh, yeah, isn't that great? Oh, yeah.
很不错  他听起来是个好人
So, uh, yeah, pretty good.He sounds like a nice, good guy.
的确  他简直太完美了
Oh, he is. And he is so dreamy.
你知道吗  他走了以后  我还说…
I mean, you know what?When he left, I actually used the phrase...
哈米娜…
..."homina, homina, homina."
好极了
That's excellent.
所以他只是个好人
So he's just a nice guy.
你真觉得  马克是不求回报的帮你
You really think this Mark doesn't want anything in exchange for helping you?
也许我该陪他洗个鸳鸯浴
Well, I assume I'll have to take showers with him.
不过哪份工作不是这样
But, you know, that's true of any job.
感觉如何
How you feeling?
我的公寓不见了
Well, my apartment isn't there anymore...
因为全被我喝光了
...because I drank it.
你去哪儿  你拆了礼物之后  我们就找不到你了
Where'd you get to? We lost you after you opened up all the presents.
对  我躲到储藏室  而且不只我一人
Yeah, I ended up in the storage room,and not alone.
真的
Really? Aah.
别叫了  别叫了
No "woo-hooing." No "woo-hooing."
怎么了  出了什么事
Why, what happened?
我跟乔伊的姐妹瞎搞
I fooled around with Joey's sister.
那还不是最糟的部分  还有更糟的吗
Well, that's not the worst part. What is the worst part?
我不记得是哪一个妹妹
I can't remember which sister.
看到了吗   别说男人有好的
You see what men do? Don't tell me men are nice.
这就是男人
This is men.
你疯了吗
Are you insane?
乔伊会杀了你  他真的会让你死得很惨
Joey's gonna kill you.He's actually going to kill you dead.
你以为我没想过吗
Okay. You don't think I thought of that?
你怎会不知道是哪一个  真令人难以置信
How can you not know which one? I mean, that's unbelievable.
是吉娜吗   吉娜是哪一位
I mean, was it Gina? Which one is Gina?
褐色蓬蓬头  戴飞机耳环的
The dark, big hair,with the airplane earrings.
不  那不是吉娜  那是迪娜  你们看  连你们也分不清
No, no, no, that's not Gina, that's Dina. See? You can't tell which is which either. Blah.
但我们没和她们瞎搞
We didn't fool around with any of them. Blah. Blah.
薇若妮卡  一定是她  穿红色裙子的
Veronica. Look, it's gotta be Veronica.The girl in the red skirt.
我确定我有把舌头伸进她嘴里
I definitely stuck my tongue down her throat.
那个是我
That was me.
喝了酒以后  我有时会太热情
Oh. When I've been drinking, sometimes I tend to get overly friendly.
对不起  没关系
And I'm sorry. That's okay.
不要紧  没关系
That's all right. That's okay.
可以跟你谈谈吗
Can I talk to you for a second?
嗨  乔伊  嗨
Hey, Joey. Hey.
过来
Come on.
不能在这里谈吗   这里有人作证
Why can't we talk in here,with witnesses?
我刚和我妹妹通过电话   哪一个
I just got off the phone with my sister. Uh, which one?
玛莉安琪拉   玛莉安琪拉
Mary Angela. Mary Angela.
对   这又是哪一个
Yeah. Now, which one is she again?
问钱德   他和她厮混过
Ask Chandler.He's the one who fooled around with her.
她告诉我  你说你有可能会爱上她
She told me you said you could really fall for her.
是真的  还是你利用她忘掉珍妮丝
Now, is that true, or are you just getting over Janice by groping my sister?
一定是前者
It's gotta be the first one.
真的吗
Really?
太好了
That's great.
你和我妹妹   坐在同一棵树下
You and my sister, sitting in a tree.
没错  我在树下
Yep, I'm in a tree.
他打来了吗   马克来电了吗
Did he call? Did Mark call?
没有  亲爱的  我很抱歉  但周末还没结束
No, honey, I'm sorry. But the weekend's not over yet.
我的老天  那是菲比吗
Oh, my God. Is that Phoebe?
大概约会回来了
Guess they're back from their date. Ah.
音乐  非常好
Music. Very nice.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你今天好吗
So how are you?
我很好  完成一本书   真的吗   关于什么的
I am good. I finished my book. Oh, yeah? What's it about?
不记得了  你想散散步吗
I don't remember.Do you wanna take a walk?
好啊
Yeah, I do.
"亲爱的玛莉安琪拉
"Dear Mary Angela:
你好吗
Hi, how's it going?
这是我写过最难以下笔的信"
This is the hardest letter I've ever had to write."
你是怎么搞的  乔伊会怎么反应…
What the hell's the matter with you? How do you think Joey's gonna react...
当他发现你写信跟她妹妹分手
...when he finds out you blew off his sister with a letter?
到那时你就告诉他  我搬到法国去了…
That's the part where you tell him that I moved to France...
但其实我会在古巴
...when actually I'll be in Cuba.
听着  你得自己来  好吗
All right, look, look,you've got to do this yourself, okay?
亲自去  至少你已经知道她的名字
In person. At least you know her name.
只要到他们家找玛莉安琪拉就行了
You just go to the house and you ask for Mary Angela, okay?
不管到门前的是哪一位…
When whichever one she is comes to the door...
带她去走走  好好谈谈
...take her for a walk,you let her down easy.
好
Okay.
万一是她来开门  而我还要求找她呢
What if Mary Angela comes to the door and I ask for Mary Angela?
你会在古巴的哪里
Where in Cuba?
乔伊  你怎么在这里
Joey, what...? What are you doing here?
等外婆把我的衣服洗好
Waiting for my grandma to finish my laundry.
那你呢
What about you?
我来找玛莉安琪拉
Uh, I'm here to see Mary Angela.
你真是男子汉  进来
You are so the man. Come on.
注意听
Now, look, listen. Listen.
你得保持沉着  因为我外婆不晓得你们俩的事
You gotta be cool, because my grandma doesn't know about you two.
最好别把她惹毛
You do not wanna tick her off.
她是第六个在墨索里尼尸体上吐痰的人
She was, like, the sixth person to spit on Mussolini's hanging body.
真的
Yeah.
玛莉安琪拉呢
Where's Mary Angela?
就在里面  好
She's right in there. Okay.
嗨  钱德  嗨  钱德
Hey, Chandler.
我不敢相信  马克居然没打来  都礼拜天了还没消息
I can't believe Mark didn't call.It's Sunday night and he didn't call.
真可惜
Bummer.
对  看看你  简直开心死了
Yeah, right. Look at you.You're practically giddy.
不  我很遗憾马克没有帮到你
No, I'm genuinely sorry the Mark thing didn't work out.
听着  瑞秋  我也希望你顺利
Look, Rach,I want only good things for you.
等等  你为什么不打给他
Wait a minute.Why don't you just call Mark?
谁规定你只能被动等待
Who says you have to sit here and wait for him?
你应该主动争取
You've got to make stuff happen.
是没错  但也不能过分主动
Yeah, but you don't wanna seem too pushy.
不会的  他把家里电话给她了
Honey, it's not pushy.He gave her his home number.
什么  家里电话  他家里的电话
Wha...? He gave you his home number,as in, like, to his home?
对  你不介意吧  因为你希望我顺利
Yeah. And you don't mind if I call,because you only want good things for me.
没错  这是好事  我是这么说的
That's right, good things.That is what I said.
哈罗  马克吗  我是瑞秋葛林
Ahem. Hello, Mark? Hi, it's Rachel Green.
喔  不  你不需要道歉
Ha, ha. Oh, no. Don't you apologize.
好  我等
Yeah, I'll hold.
他把我的电话放在公司
He left my number at work.
本来要去拿  但他得帮侄女做报告
He was gonna get it, but he was helping his niece with her report on the pioneers.
真会扯
Aw. That is so made up.
我  我的天  明天  真是…不  太好了
Yeah. Oh, my God. Tomorrow? That's... No, it's perfect.
天哪  太感谢你了 太好了  再见
Oh, God. Thank you so much.Great. Bye.
我得到面试机会了
Oh! I got the interview.
你看吧
Oh, yay! There you go.
他还约我吃午餐  帮我准备
He even offered to meet me for lunch and prep me for it.
太棒了  对啊
Oh, that is amazing. Yeah.
如果我了解马克  我想我是…
Well, if I know Mark, and I think I do...
他应该就是那么棒  我得想想要穿什么
...I'd expect nothing less. I gotta figure out what I'm gonna wear.
高领衫加垮裤  看起来比较专业
High collar and baggy pants say,"I'm a pro."
好吧  回头见  好
Yeah, right. Okay, I'll see you guys later. Woo-hoo! Okay.
你行的
You go get them.
我对你不好吗  我有伤害过你吗
What did I do to you? Did I hurt you in some way?
什么  "你为什么不打给他"
What? "Why don't you call him?"
多亏你  他现在要帮她准备面试
Well, thank you very much.Now he's gonna prep her.
帮忙准备面试  下一步就是要开除男友了
You know, prep her, as in what you do before you surgically remove the boyfriend.
你有病啊
Are you crazy?
有吗  有吗  我失去理智了吗
Oh, am I? Am I? Am I out of my mind? Am I losing my senses?
这个完美男要跟我女友吃饭
This dreamy guy is taking my girlfriend out for a meal.
罗斯  这跟你无关
Ross, you know, this isn't even about you.
这关系到瑞秋和她的前途
This is about Rache land something happening for her.
就算你是对的
Uh-huh.Even if you're right.
他可能另有所图  表示他就能得逞吗
What if he wants to sleep with her? Does that mean he gets to?
也不是  但… 你不信任她吗
No, but... I mean, don't you trust her?
没有
Well, yeah...
那就说服你自己  成熟点
Then get over yourself. Grow up.
你才成熟点
You grow up.
这提拉米苏太棒了
This tiramisu is excellent.
是你做的吗  玛莉安琪拉  不  是我做的
Did you make it, Mary Angela? No, I did.
真美味
Well, it's yummy.
那玛莉安琪拉  你喜欢吗
So, uh, Mary Angela, do you like it?
当然  这是她的最爱
Of course. It's her favorite.
所以…
So, um, hmm...
玛莉安琪拉  你还喜欢什么
Mary Angela,what's your second favorite?
更多的是外婆做的提拉米苏
More of Grandma's tiramisu.
拜托你…
Oh, would you just please...
把食谱给我  因为它太好吃了
...give me your recipe,because this is great.
最棒的
It's top-notch.
食谱要跟着我上天堂   我也是
That dies with me. So will I.
想办法到浴室来
Excuse yourself and go to the bathroom.
我只是眯着眼睛  没有任何意思
Oh, no, I was just squinting.That doesn't mean anything.
做就对了
Just do it.
失陪一下  我得…
Will you excuse me? I have to, um...
喂
Hey...
总算  我还以为没机会和你独处  听我说句话好吗
Finally. I thought we'd never be alone. Can I just tell you something?
派对结束之后  我满脑子都在想着你
I have not stopped thinking about you since the party.
听着  我可能操之过急了
Look, I may have jumped the gun here.Whoa.
我刚结束一段感情
I just got out of a relationship.
我还没办法… 给任何人承诺
And I'm not really in a...In a commitment kind of place.
所以呢   我也不想
So? Me neither.
天啊  玛莉安琪拉说的没错  你的双唇真柔软
God, Mary Angela was right.You do have the softest lips.
你不是玛莉安琪拉  不  我是玛莉泰瑞丝
You're not Mary Angela? No. I'm Mary Therese.
太糟糕了
This is so bad.
如果你不是玛莉安琪拉  那谁是
If you're not Mary Angela, then who is?
是我
I am.
糟糕
Oh, it's so bad.
乔伊  别叫乔伊  别叫他
No Joey. No Joey. No Joey.
乔伊  什么事
Joey. What's going on?
换你了  快跑去躲起来
You're it. Now run and hide.
没什么
It's no big deal.
钱德吻了我  他以为我是玛莉安琪拉
Chandler was just kissing me because he thought I was Mary Angela.
什么  你怎么会  把她当成玛丽安琪拉
What? How could you do that? How could you think she was Mary Angela?
我不确定哪位是玛莉安琪拉
I wasn't sure which one Mary Angela was.
听着  我很抱歉  好吗
Look, I'm sorry, okay?
我那天很醉  你们的样子都差不多
I was really drunk,and you guys all look really similar.
揍他  乔伊
I say punch him, Joey.
对  揍他  对  踢他
Yeah, punch him. Yeah, kick him.
我们应该冷静一点…
We should all calm down...
因为  你们的兄弟不会打我的
...because, you know,your brother's not gonna punch me.
对吧
Are you?
我通常会这么做
Well, that is usually what I would do.
但我没想过被揍的会是你
But I never thought you'd be on the receiving end.
你怎么能这样
How could you do this?
乔伊  如果你想揍我  尽管来  我活该
Joey, if you wanna punch me, go ahead.I deserve it.
我只想说  我从未想过要伤害你  或你的家人
But I just want you to know that I would never soberly hurt you or your family.
你是我最好的朋友
You're my best friend.
我再也不会做这种事了
And I would never do anything like this ever again.
所以呢
So what?
我说揍他  揍他  对  揍他
I say punch him. Punch him. Yeah, punch him.
来吧  揍他  不  我不会揍钱德
Come on, punch him. No. No. I'm not gonna punch Chandler.
让我来  不行
I'll do it.No, you won't.
他知道错了  而且我相信他
Look, he knows he did a terrible thing,and I believe him.
他很抱歉  但你还需向一个人道歉
He's sorry.But you got one more apology to make.
懂吗   你得向玛莉安琪拉道歉
All right? You gotta apologize to Mary Angela.
好  没问题  你说的对  好
Okay. Absolutely. You got it. All right.
甜心  现在你可以揍他了  什么
Cookie, now you can punch him. What?
嘿  嗨
Hey. Hi.
你怎么来了
What are you doing here?
刚好顺路
You know,this building's on my paper route, so...
嗨  嗨
Oh. Hi.Hi.
顺利吗
How did it go?
面试我的女人很难对付…
Oh, well, the woman I interviewed with was pretty tough...
但幸好  马克有指导我
...but, you know,thank God Mark coached me.
我一提到秋季新装  她便开心极了
Once I started talking about the fall line,she got all happy.
我真为你骄傲  我也是
I'm so proud of you. Me too.
听我说  我…
Listen, I'm, uh...
很抱歉我这么敏感又嫉妒…
I'm sorry I've been so crazy and jealous and...
只是  我很喜欢你  所以…
It's just, I like you a lot, so...
我懂
I know.
真的吗  真的
Yeah? Yeah.
瑞秋  是的
Rachel. Yeah?
嗨  嗨  马克
Hi. Hi. Hi, Mark.
我刚和乔安娜谈过  她很欣赏你  你被录取了
I just talked to Joanna, and she loves you.You got it. You got the job.
真的吗  我录取了
What? Oh! I did?
没错
Yes.
我的天
Aah! Oh, my God!
恭喜你
Congratulations... Oh! Wow.
菲比  你的约会怎么样
So, Phoebe.Hmm? How was your date?
你知道的
Oh, well, you know. Ha, ha.
我的确知道
Yeah, I do know.
你们偷听吗
Ick. You were eavesdropping?
偷听  菲比  天花板的磁砖  都快掉下来了
Eavesdropping? Pheebs, the ceiling tiles were falling down.
我很抱歉
Oh, I'm sorry.
但我真的很喜欢这个人  我想他也喜欢我
But I really like this guy,and I think he really happens to like me.
也许他正在玩弹跳床  而且很投入
Maybe he's just jumping on a pogo stick and he really likes it.
也许弹跳床也乐在其中
Maybe the pogo stick likes it too.
够了  到此为止  他不能这样对菲比
All right, that's it.He cannot do this to Phoebe.
他该被痛扁一顿
This guy's gonna get the butt-kickingof a lifetime.
他块头很大吗
But is he a big guy?
我们一起去  走吧
We'll all go. Come on.
谢谢你们  谢谢  别担心
Thanks, you guys. Thank you.Don't worry.
老天  我希望他被痛扁
God. I hope they kick his ass.
亲爱的  我很遗憾
Honey, I'm sorry.
如果这样说能安慰你的话…
You know, if it's any consolation...
他跟你在一起时听起来比较开心
...he really did sound like he was having more fun with you.